{"data":{"createNewExamAttempt":{"attempt":{"id":"c15c79dc-da10-46cf-a345-8657674be217"},"exam":{"id":"54b212a2-0b47-47bf-93d0-c586a915d182","title":"AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam","duration":5400,"totalQuestions":65,"questions":[{"id":"a4a20c80-1512-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following statements are true of Amazon Aurora?","explanation":"Amazon Aurora is compatible with MySQL and PostgreSQL, and you can handle routine database tasks on it using either the AWS Management Console, AWS CLI commands, or API operations. As a relational database offering, it is part of the RDS service, not DynamoDB, which is AWS’s nonrelational database service. In addition, Aurora delivers up to five times the throughput of MySQL, not three times.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/AuroraUserGuide/CHAP_AuroraOverview.html","title":"What is Amazon Aurora?"}],"answers":[{"id":"16e59a8af37a34b9625d2d16558ef925","text":"It is part of the Amazon DynamoDB service.","correct":false},{"id":"ca3a9ff8718b6a2ed0c56d839b5313b0","text":"It can deliver up to three times the throughput of MySQL.","correct":false},{"id":"87b549b9a5f186a6d978ec037b9d268f","text":"It uses the AWS Management Console, AWS CLI commands, and API operations to handle routine database tasks.","correct":true},{"id":"542b22f6c50dd511f8e64db1ac734bc6","text":"It is compatible with the MySQL and PostgreSQL database engines.","correct":true}]},{"id":"trwylx1o-zl9g-9de6-rxeg-gp4pakkifop1","domain":"tech","question":"The load on your application fluctuates by day of the week. Wednesdays have the most traffic; Saturdays have the least traffic. Which AWS service allows you to ensure you have the correct amount of compute capacity while also optimizing on a cost basis? ","explanation":"Auto Scaling allows you to add or remove EC2 instances based on conditions you specify. Auto-Scaling events can be scheduled to meet predictable changes in the load on your application.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/","title":"About Auto Scaling"}],"answers":[{"id":"afd14eb3f151c84e6ef7ab63812b4fbc","text":"Auto Scaling","correct":true},{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":false},{"id":"739749e0ec278613ef4f8e6861efc722","text":"Trusted Advisor","correct":false},{"id":"a2c64f657687c46ed9811761849051e4","text":"EC2 Container Service","correct":false}]},{"id":"b1acc5ea-cc62-4f91-9d0c-badb7c8ef957","domain":"tech","question":"You have been tasked with creating identical, repeatable Infrastructure for your customers. Which service will you use?","explanation":"CloudFormation provides the ability to provision a repeatedly deployable environment for your customers, CloudFront is a Content Delivery Network used to Cache content across the world. CloudWatch is used for telemetry and AWS Config is used to assess, audit and evaluate the configurations of your AWS resources.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/","title":"AWS Auto Scaling"}],"answers":[{"id":"58e3bfbabf904de43a6a22aca509b0d8","text":"CloudFormation","correct":true},{"id":"2d80a80d60fea86242f99512dbac7529","text":"AWS Config","correct":false},{"id":"bef6cb89241de238f082cb243307ad1b","text":"CloudFront","correct":false},{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":false}]},{"id":"55632ec1-3922-4d04-80c0-ff9b5b21c2d2","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following are AWS EC2 reserved pricing types?","explanation":"Reserved instances have three main pricing models, Standard, Convertible and Scheduled. Each model is targeted with a specific use case and benefits from its own level of discounted price","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"c81edad1f6d23ac52025cde1cf22ba7b","text":"Scheduled Reserved Instances","correct":true},{"id":"e507a844b940fd588a1cbb5bb46fd4fe","text":"Standard Reserved Instances","correct":true},{"id":"c9e63a71aa24afcde5e964d2530e2524","text":"Compute Reserved Instances","correct":false},{"id":"bd1ad3385adf098b2e87d2bb75d87e39","text":"Scalable Reserved Instances","correct":false},{"id":"fe501a6493589e0d87e90fd0b4361e6f","text":"Convertable Reserved Instances","correct":true}]},{"id":"30rp7hn8-3uti-zql0-ays0-x3qfjnnnaax9","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are geographic areas that host two or more Availability Zones?","explanation":"A Region is a geographic area that hosts two or more Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":true},{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"2bdbf4724b81ff0529e32fdb1af28130","text":"AWS Origins","correct":false},{"id":"0ed2343b7ec3f778399e20cf93f8f507","text":"Compute Zones","correct":false}]},{"id":"m62nhm8n-lhqq-ymv5-2qs9-9zn2hm7gh6qt","domain":"tech","question":"You need to execute code in response to a specific change to your S3 bucket. Which of the following compute services should you choose to execute your code?","explanation":"Lambda is event-driven: a change to an S3 bucket is an example of an Event.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/","title":"About Lambda"}],"answers":[{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"c8f63ecaff5e983a2441126a241c4cfa","text":"ECS","correct":false},{"id":"b21eea42e76007ac061cf37a5a41037d","text":"Lightsail","correct":false},{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":true}]},{"id":"e9yzvx4u-z9ss-opgg-lwg4-h390rywj4hat","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following AWS services controls Authentication and Authorization within an AWS account?","explanation":"IAM (Identity and Access Management) controls Authentication and Authorization within an AWS account. Security Groups and Access Control Lists are tools within IAM that can help make that control easier to manage. AWS Shield is a separate service that helps protect resources from external attacks.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/details/","title":"About IAM"}],"answers":[{"id":"303a25c2935ec1fdb01208b6f4f65688","text":"Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":true},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false}]},{"id":"07a07fe6-1500-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following engines are classified as relational databases on AWS?","explanation":"PostgreSQL, MySQL, and Oracle are three types of RDS engines on AWS. By contrast, DynamoDB is Amazon’s nonrelational database solution and RedShift is Amazon's data warehouse service.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/","title":"Amazon Relational Database Service (RDS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"62a004b95946bb97541afa471dcca73a","text":"MySQL","correct":true},{"id":"30162ed78b6c10f731411f2fc440c24f","text":"Oracle","correct":true},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"399bd1ee587245ecac6f39beaa99886f","text":"PostgreSQL","correct":true},{"id":"35f802e4a5e1cbdf3f99a71a86ae3153","text":"RedShift","correct":false}]},{"id":"83246738-477a-40c5-8224-59d739ad6600","domain":"tech","question":"You are a solutions architect working for a New York-based digital marketing company specializing in local SEO. You are tasked with creating an S3 bucket to operate within the US West (N. California) Region. The company wants to name it with the IP address of the SEO Health Checker application that was recently developed for potential clients based in California to get a free website analysis report. Which of these actions would be most appropriate?","explanation":"Bucket names must not be formatted as an IP address. Indeed, each bucket name should be unique across all existing names in Amazon S3. So, following AWS naming rules, name the bucket after the type of data it will store.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/BucketRestrictions.html","title":"Bucket Restrictions and Limitations"}],"answers":[{"id":"557ad9f77b4777473a400e65c0bc146a","text":"Do not name the bucket after the application’s IP address.","correct":true},{"id":"73d20a8bf6fd3ae4e325f0aba2e8a8c6","text":"Use dashes instead of periods in the IP address to comply with bucket naming rules.","correct":false},{"id":"49336715d3a6034152315aaa72ba1ca2","text":"That shouldn’t be a problem; name the bucket after the web application’s IP address.","correct":false},{"id":"dc1cf44cc05f915cfa69e23237b4e6c0","text":"Simply name the bucket after the Region.","correct":false}]},{"id":"01355a86-1c9a-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"In Amazon EC2, which of the following do you use to log into Linux instances?","explanation":"To log into Linux instances using EC2, you will need a key pair; Windows instances are the ones that need a user name and password to log in. Multi-factor authentication (MFA) involves the addition of an extra layer of protection, such as a code generated from an authenticator, to a user name and password. MFA can be enabled to use with IAM, or Identity and Access Management.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction_security-outside-iam.html","title":"Security Features Outside of IAM"}],"answers":[{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":false},{"id":"6cd56a4cc4ddbbfd2bc9d57de5d788aa","text":"Key pair","correct":true},{"id":"1a504cebc3822fd967eb6426a7ff0a31","text":"Multi-factor authentication","correct":false},{"id":"f3499a9f28ab4d9412f8dc5e818c8ccd","text":"User name and password","correct":false}]},{"id":"97909ec2-34ad-4743-b7cc-ca2c83c62cc1","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following statements are true of the AWS Free Tier?","explanation":"The AWS Free Tier offers some services for free for the first 12 months after signing up for an AWS account. It also offers free trials of select AWS services for a short period. So, usage is governed by these principles. Although there are some service usages that are always free, this does not apply to EC2 Micro instances nor S3 storage of up to 5 GB.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"f60585d833d73cf82fda96da1f19b3e6","text":"Some AWS services come with short-term free trial offers.","correct":true},{"id":"c90c4c865ee803cfa9bbe8e9a2d845c9","text":"Amazon S3 storage of up to 5 GB is always free.","correct":false},{"id":"42c6d3d9032dba4f7aea8ddeedde2f6c","text":"You will never be charged for use of EC2 Micro instances.","correct":false},{"id":"424553c7a1502a98737dfd15823ee215","text":"Some AWS services are free for the first 12 months following the initial sign-up date to AWS.","correct":true}]},{"id":"520b9022-2fa7-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Your company needs the support of concierge-level account specialists to help with billing and account subjects. Which of the following AWS Support pricing plans provides that feature?","explanation":"Only the Enterprise support plan will provide a Concierge Support Team, which is a group of account specialists to assist your company with their billing and accounting questions.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"AWS Support Plans"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/enterprise/","title":"AWS Enterprise Support"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false}]},{"id":"86ed7d54-4495-435b-908a-b439c255c35d","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the five best practices does AWS Trusted Advisor use to eliminate unused, underutilized, and idle resources in your environment?","explanation":"AWS Trusted Advisor ensures cost optimization of your AWS account by eliminating unused, underutilized, and idle resources, which include EC2 instances, load balancers, EBS volumes, and elastic IP addresses.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/trusted-advisor/best-practice-checklist/","title":"AWS Trusted Advisor Best Practice Checks"}],"answers":[{"id":"9446a98ad14416153cc4d45ab8b531bf","text":"Performance","correct":false},{"id":"07d2fdfae089a6e085811b22437de261","text":"Service limits","correct":false},{"id":"2fae32629d4ef4fc6341f1751b405e45","text":"Security","correct":false},{"id":"a39ae09f8be4327fc176cfeb76a0e366","text":"Cost optimization","correct":true},{"id":"45a75e44a713fdf94dbf1dbaa0749188","text":"Fault tolerance","correct":false}]},{"id":"eaf197bf-a9f1-4611-90be-dbcf7364c74a","domain":"concepts","question":"You have an application load balancer for routing traffic from developers to the EC2 instance that contains a web application being put into operation. To prepare for the application going live for public use, you add an Auto Scaling Group and a second application load balancer to route web traffic from customers to the EC2 instance. The addition is an example of which of the following:","explanation":"This is an example of scalability, which means that systems are expected to grow over time with no drop in performance. ","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"2166e76dc88d642260416a536b06a412","text":"Durability","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"820b8f74ad843d1574106ec4cadfc07e","text":"Reliability","correct":false}]},{"id":"rqfj1uaw-51ci-mvl2-1djk-uzefaek5cehy","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is correct?","explanation":"The number of Edge Locations is greater than the number of Availability Zones, which is greater than the number of Regions. Regions contain Availability Zones, therefore there will always be more AZs than Regions.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"27268ba761c3ae0dbf9e4c8959f13e0f","text":"# of Availability Zones > # of Regions > # of Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"916cfd186ad7a451ebd785b35c738429","text":"# of Edge Locations > # of Availability Zones > # of Regions","correct":true},{"id":"07ebe9ccf5e5396c2f2c81de53d3829e","text":"# of Regions > # of Availability Zones > # of Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"3782de3e5fc87f6e1a21193778c0d5bf","text":"# of Availability Zones > # of Edge Locations > # of Regions","correct":false}]},{"id":"5l7vjhuv-wf9j-de1i-9aj4-e9dlg8u6cc76","domain":"billing","question":"Your Development team uses four on-demand EC2 instances, and your QA team has 5 reserved instances, only three of which are being used. Assuming all AWS accounts are under a single AWS Organization, how will the Development team's instances be billed?","explanation":"Assuming all instances are in the same AWS Organization, the reserved instance pricing for the unused QA instances will be applied to two of the four Dev instances.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/reserved-instances/pricing/","title":"EC2 Instance Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"ecadbc09799c3807dfed5bd9ee9c6159","text":"All the Dev team's instances will be billed at the on-demand rate.","correct":false},{"id":"b04b07a9c68b5b505f53afccb5616743","text":"The pricing for the reserved instances will shift from QA to Dev.","correct":false},{"id":"3ea9a50157f205cce00d0db169117711","text":"All the Dev instances will be billed at the reserved instance rate.","correct":false},{"id":"a6d19cc18b59af08baaa0f8247fca355","text":"The Dev team will be billed for two instances at on-demand prices and two instances at the reserved instance price.","correct":true}]},{"id":"ef918c09-219a-45b3-b1cc-f5b02cdbfc1d","domain":"concepts","question":"What type of placement group should you use to spread Amazon EC2 instances across logical partitions so that they don’t share the same underlying hardware?","explanation":"With a partition placement group, EC2 instances are placed into logical segments called partitions, each of which has its own set of racks to supply its network and power source. This level of isolation is designed to prevent the impact of hardware failure within your application.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/placement-groups.html","title":"Placement Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"3349300356cb3141ea939dcbdf749789","text":"Partition","correct":true},{"id":"66f9c6c5b672ee16deeef6e4503cb4bc","text":"Reserve","correct":false},{"id":"180bc3b1c5619aaef40e803f49921012","text":"Spread","correct":false},{"id":"249694a485fc5d3289c38986b4f8e887","text":"Cluster","correct":false}]},{"id":"5a168390-1f66-11ea-a5e8-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"You added a recently hired HR Assistant to the IAM group named 'HumanResources'. Which of the following statements will apply to that user?","explanation":"By adding the HR Assistant to the 'HumanResources' group by using the AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) service, the new hiree is now a member of the company’s HR department and inherits the administrative permissions of that group.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/getting-started_create-admin-group.html","title":"Create Your First IAM Admin User and Group"}],"answers":[{"id":"a445a3cad5d84550114916ae6df763c4","text":"The HR Assistant becomes leader of the Human Resources department.","correct":false},{"id":"4f98907d2b5e12fad173f30f4d61ec84","text":"The HR Assistant inherits the permissions of the 'HumanResources' group.","correct":true},{"id":"b098a137cb3a11528e46deb8c5aff98d","text":"The HR Assistant becomes an IAM member of the company’s Human Resources department.","correct":true},{"id":"367051fc494f2dba53682af0d5f9a9e1","text":"The HR Assistant becomes the AWS root account user.","correct":false}]},{"id":"aabc59b3-b883-454e-8336-dac6f49eb7c3","domain":"security","question":"You are a Systems Administrator who has just started adding IAM users to your company’s AWS account. However, you worry that the users will not create passwords strong enough to prevent unauthorized access. What is the most reliable way to ensure that users are using strong passwords?","explanation":"Use Identity and Access Management (IAM) to apply an IAM password policy. While awareness and training are critical to developing good security practices, the most reliable option is to use an IAM Password Policy, which won't allow users to use lower strength passwords.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_credentials_passwords_account-policy.html?icmpid=docs_iam_console","title":"Setting an Account Password Policy for IAM Users"}],"answers":[{"id":"a08ccc3650b327c02cd13367d8ffa875","text":"Hold an AWS webinar to stress the importance of creating strong passwords.","correct":false},{"id":"2ef38712519600d72d012e44a6dcb5a3","text":"Ask for the password of each user and create a much stronger one by yourself.","correct":false},{"id":"6cb5679faafdf0c247c2543bdca0e635","text":"Apply an IAM password policy to ensure users create appropriately strong passwords.","correct":true},{"id":"da197ad4fa2d98027feab02afd84d7fc","text":"Speak with each IAM user individually about the importance of creating strong passwords.","correct":false}]},{"id":"11cddf60-2bb5-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services is an example of Platform as a Service?","explanation":"Platform as a Service, or PaaS, enables the development, running, and management of applications on the cloud without the need to build and maintain any infrastructure. That is precisely what Elastic Beanstalk provides; the ability to quickly deploy and manage applications in the AWS Cloud without worrying about the infrastructure that runs those applications. Elastic Beanstalk is the only PaaS listed here.","links":[{"url":"https: //aws.amazon.com/elasticbeanstalk/","title":"AWS Elastic Beanstalk"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/types-of-cloud-computing/","title":"Types of Cloud Computing"}],"answers":[{"id":"dee7ff8f7b10b9d388c7c561e9413b0d","text":"AWS Lambda","correct":false},{"id":"c33dcb724e4d74e54dbc8347d4402690","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud","correct":false},{"id":"270fcb785810d0206945029bb05f4e97","text":"Amazon S3","correct":false},{"id":"bcf6eb183b7da148701bcc059a34675f","text":"AWS Elastic Beanstalk","correct":true}]},{"id":"ai3ijdez-wtig-dn7p-p04b-jb32lm26m7cb","domain":"tech","question":"In order to comply with regulatory mandates, some of your data needs to be retained in perpetuity. Which of the following AWS storage services offers low-cost, long-term data archival?","explanation":"Glacier is your best choice for deeply-discounted, long-term object archival - as long as the data does not need to be available and online at a moment's notice.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/glacier/","title":"About Glacier"}],"answers":[{"id":"4def2a084469f97f6372bfaf0823941b","text":"Glacier","correct":true},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":false},{"id":"f332127ba5ee3389e4c5cff45ac9a518","text":"EFS","correct":false},{"id":"f52a9d91766886fb3a524dd06d1581cb","text":"Redshift","correct":false}]},{"id":"7ed103d1-670b-487f-aa14-6d5e29084eb2","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following Amazon EC2 pricing models automatically adjusts charges as your usage changes?","explanation":"Savings Plans is the only Amazon EC2 pricing model that provides the flexibility of adjusting charges depending on the amount of usage, thereby saving money in the process.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/savingsplans/","title":"Savings Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"29068f6044e3fedf44165e646a2d2bb1","text":"Reserved Instances","correct":false},{"id":"acbe4e201e8e2ac67830983f9c8d7970","text":"Dedicated Hosts","correct":false},{"id":"e26ff95de7b422fa8d7999578d2becc3","text":"On-Demand","correct":false},{"id":"b9912bfb6c79dc963ccc7e74d0ef9b36","text":"Savings Plan","correct":true}]},{"id":"11337c6a-2fe1-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following statements is true of Amazon Aurora?","explanation":"The only statement that is not true is Response A. Aurora is compatible with MySQL and PostgresSQL, but not with MariaDB.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/AuroraUserGuide/CHAP_AuroraOverview.html","title":"What is Amazon Aurora?"}],"answers":[{"id":"e17ce0919bb302cc40193f3b80181176","text":"It can auto-scale up to 64 TB of storage space.","correct":true},{"id":"df120e572996d59e2f2d7eb17eea6c1a","text":"It is compatible with MariaDB.","correct":false},{"id":"2b4cdcd7f9dc266e76ab58a968be68b5","text":"It can deliver up to five times the throughput of MySQL.","correct":true},{"id":"02a6a3634e2fbdb506decbb529496d8a","text":"It is a Relational Database Service (RDS) database engine developed by Amazon.","correct":true}]},{"id":"89c58d68-554a-45ea-9da8-fcf90103d4e8","domain":"concepts","question":"The Chief Marketing Officer of the hotel chain you work for would like to implement voice recognition capabilities in rooms so customers can request services without picking up the phone. Competitors have already begun rolling out these technologies in an attempt to improve their customers’ experience. Which benefit of the AWS cloud would you most emphasize to the CMO in your business case for creating an AWS-based solution?","explanation":"The AWS cloud provides instant access to new technologies. Companies can move with agility to satisfy new business requirements and meet competitive demands. There is a very low barrier of entry for innovation. If a solution is not meeting expectations, services can be instantly de-provisioned. The other three options will also prove to be benefits of deploying in the AWS cloud, but the use case emphasizes the need to move quickly against competitive threats.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"6cdf2174e24cf3e60f016e85f00c34ff","text":"Deploy Globally in Minutes","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"ecbe6eb71bcb646d89d2e361dfa84c21","text":"Cost Savings","correct":false},{"id":"241bb470b0110efc8b5609f7311b0bb1","text":"Agility","correct":true}]},{"id":"ltl6jev0-2f05-xevd-rnut-yi3l7ar7nzk1","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound design when it comes to reliability?","explanation":"The elasticity of cloud computing means that you never need to over-provision or manage change at the resource level.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"c57c5e34d89769a30ca48ef1c1155033","text":"Scale horizontally.","correct":true},{"id":"25ddbfce9d53b8f5a9e09aad85948b96","text":"Stop guessing about your capacity requirements.","correct":true},{"id":"7f20528f07a394778f02e20e5453fc02","text":"When in doubt, over-provision.","correct":false},{"id":"2c081b2e4ef662d134361511c0f138e1","text":"Manage change at the individual resource level.","correct":false}]},{"id":"3f2cee98-aedc-43ec-a5f6-2de9a48a9885","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following engines are classified as relational databases on AWS?","explanation":"Aurora and MariaDB are two types of RDS engines on AWS. Redshift is for data warehousing, and DynamoDB is Amazon’s non-relational database solution.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/","title":"Amazon Relational Database Service (RDS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"7f9733e208088b1ce6df3d4be1765396","text":"MariaDB","correct":true},{"id":"f52a9d91766886fb3a524dd06d1581cb","text":"Redshift","correct":false},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"509e0895bd82e3315e79018a6ce02181","text":"Aurora","correct":true}]},{"id":"ij3guy5r-65pf-5sad-nyrn-vkpusbdxd3cz","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services can assist you with cost optimization?","explanation":"Trusted Advisor can assist you with the cost optimization of your AWS environment.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"About Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":true},{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":false}]},{"id":"bccfe3b0-61d9-4680-81cc-45a78d8a722d","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following options are available for configuring a password policy for IAM users of an AWS account?","explanation":"The password policy options does not include the requirement of using at least one numerical character from 1 to 9; it is actually at least one numerical character from 0 to 9. Passwords can contain between 6 to 128 characters, so 12 to 64 characters is incorrect. The other three options listed are correct.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_credentials_passwords_account-policy.html?icmpid=docs_iam_console","title":"Setting an Account Password Policy for IAM Users"}],"answers":[{"id":"7115f92e53f08f3e583dcfde0a88161b","text":"Use at least one numerical character from 1 to 9.","correct":false},{"id":"454e4156bef76a1758de1fb18c771f5b","text":"Require that passwords contain at least one of the AWS-listed nonalphanumeric characters.","correct":true},{"id":"164affd52e9cf98d09976ffa798d82dd","text":"Allow users to change their passwords.","correct":true},{"id":"9fd02d6b80fbf23454be435b3ecbe598","text":"Use between 6 to 128 characters to form the password.","correct":true},{"id":"fcce064756de55a96a60925043d2feb0","text":"Use between 12 to 64 characters to form the password.","correct":false}]},{"id":"35f041db-16e3-4bb3-825d-7ab528bddd1b","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following falls under AWS compute services category?","explanation":"EC2, Lightsail, and Elastic Beanstalk fall under the compute umbrella of AWS services. EFS and AWS Backup are classified as storage services, and Amazon RDS is classified as database services.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/","title":"Amazon Web Services (AWS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"ce52d2cff6e50f2e74505e0c70d072b3","text":"AWS Backup","correct":false},{"id":"9e10649cd5a6507c47e44a66dc03eb5b","text":"Amazon Lightsail","correct":true},{"id":"765c63bdfc41e7ae2614191faa2b0d0a","text":"Amazon Elastic Beanstalk","correct":true},{"id":"d2a6652ddeb631da029d1f2806e11fdc","text":"Amazon Elastic File System (EFS)","correct":false},{"id":"98492fcf8e38ae7ea331e271498d5275","text":"Amazon Relational Database Services (RDS)","correct":false},{"id":"ce1a41ee0352cee512475ef6a6233963","text":"Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2)","correct":true}]},{"id":"464c8f56-20a3-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following types of EC2 instances is ideal for workloads that process large data sets in memory?","explanation":"True to its naming, memory optimized instances are specifically for workloads that require more memory than usual to process data.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/instance-types/","title":"Amazon EC2 Instance Types"}],"answers":[{"id":"2f925ef0b67b13f124d684b4e0ca9682","text":"Accelerated Computing","correct":false},{"id":"ea999a66bf3ccfec4616d5be49348665","text":"Storage Optimized","correct":false},{"id":"94a1a3953054d8ece597f4f69bb343d4","text":"General Purpose","correct":false},{"id":"b26f852f8cf53bd055d76deddcadf155","text":"Compute Optimized","correct":false},{"id":"fb152ac1edfe96da5fe255e395003b0d","text":"Memory Optimized","correct":true}]},{"id":"cykf25tw-ja73-62pe-bg44-2xko23ptcj2t","domain":"security","question":"Broadly speaking AWS is responsible for:","explanation":"Generally speaking, AWS is responsible for security OF the cloud - meaning that it is responsible for the infrastructure (hardware and software) which is used to deliver cloud services to customers.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"e5a10169b294451720bbfc8cee548381","text":"Security both IN and OF the cloud","correct":false},{"id":"17e0b507a41c19ff7684c3bf9d56497f","text":"None of security - security is up to the customer to manage","correct":false},{"id":"2ac2679f0084e375060c216fe7477ab4","text":"Security OF the cloud","correct":true},{"id":"2245b1bb4da8871fd09d4b5b6c52555e","text":"Security IN the cloud","correct":false}]},{"id":"f3458221-d64a-4bbb-b337-65aa47b1614e","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following does Amazon assure will happen when paying for AWS on an as-needed basis?","explanation":"Amazon provides certain benefits when you pay for services on an as-needed basis for your business. You can spend more time innovating and inventing, which consequently reduces the complexity of procurement and enables your business to be fully elastic. ","links":[{"url":"https://d0.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws_pricing_overview.pdf","title":"How AWS Pricing Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"805b488dc48f4591141569966cee0a89","text":"Enabling the full elasticity of business operations","correct":true},{"id":"4657fb4ee914ab51c07ee5913b69cb48","text":"Reducing procurement complexity","correct":true},{"id":"8c0088e02946138166ef2d9e4bf9ab82","text":"Spending less money in the long term","correct":false},{"id":"48a2453a766bcd12a90a271271ca86a5","text":"Redirecting focus to innovation and invention","correct":true},{"id":"d2c91d7ba7466b41bdbcd42e13db2ecb","text":"Spending more money in the long term","correct":false}]},{"id":"ipqdbu85-0egr-7f6l-daqk-ftz6657spa8l","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes a system that is always online — without the need for human intervention?","explanation":"A highly available system is one that is always online — without the need for human intervention. Although Fault Tolerance is closely related to High Availability, FT usually implies a degradation of service without human intervention, unlike HA which is like-for-like.","links":[{"url":"https://media.amazonwebservices.com/architecturecenter/AWS_ac_ra_ftha_04.pdf","title":"Fault Tolerance and High Availability Infographic"}],"answers":[{"id":"35d7975974b40518da5e7f990c6a7d1d","text":"Fault Tolerant","correct":false},{"id":"9818cb0bfa2dfb200a8c078b1fe1c2fd","text":"Highly Available","correct":true},{"id":"28cb2468ce3a85b4d10668ec48f5e4d6","text":"Scalable","correct":false},{"id":"a078ed5ade8df4aac54efbdb57e63ad2","text":"Elastic","correct":false}]},{"id":"a31cc98c-2146-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following scenarios demand the use of an egress-only Internet gateway?","explanation":"An egress-only Internet gateway is used for IPv6 addresses only. It allows outbound communication from instances in your VPC to the Internet, and prevents the Internet from initiating connection with the instances.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/egress-only-internet-gateway.html","title":"Egress-Only Internet Gateways"}],"answers":[{"id":"01fc59aa00d3c5c5c0ffff43b05a22a0","text":"Allowing communication to the Internet and preventing communication from the Internet over IPv4","correct":false},{"id":"5be0953999314fd060740ef201866d64","text":"Allowing communication to the Internet and preventing communication from the Internet over IPv6","correct":true},{"id":"9e839253188e9d5f95d2e2278c3bad32","text":"Allowing communication from the Internet and preventing communication to the Internet over IPv4","correct":false},{"id":"350b0f16434bcd3e211471390f1d840b","text":"Allowing communication from the Internet and preventing communication to the Internet over IPv6","correct":false}]},{"id":"5d7bea17-63ec-412b-bb14-bd0a1f5c4683","domain":"concepts","question":"If you have a new application and you are not sure about future demand, which of the below characteristics of cloud make cloud an ideal place to host it?","explanation":"No upfront & Pay as you go mean that you do not need an initial outlay of capital for resources to build in cloud, and only need to pay for what you use going forward. These combined with the ability to consume more resources when needed (Scalability) mean that cloud is a great way to host applications that have dynamic requirements. No Single Points of Failure and High Availability should be included in any design, but are not intrinsic to cloud. Similarly, although Performance Efficiency is key, this comes down to you application and it's design, and is not a characteristic of the cloud. ","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"e95a95951d99b5f038c688bf69bd5a01","text":"Pay as you go","correct":true},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"5c751a74a73417fb82a2cc45c4edc2cb","text":"No upfront","correct":true},{"id":"bc368b371822f4e7df28c5768582dde8","text":"Performance Efficiency","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"9043a5d84d85473bd60ab9b11f10b04b","text":"No single point of failure","correct":false}]},{"id":"pylft010-qst0-1uhz-wkp8-iok6z6z5m9zs","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following are payment options for Reserved Instances?","explanation":"Reserves instances are available with all upfront, partial upfront, or no upfront (AURI, PURI, and NURI) pricing.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/reserved-instances/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Reserved Instances Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"53ed2947db4516ed0087c215e7ffc748","text":"NURI","correct":true},{"id":"38cf9fac137f64bb80e2a3a31163f746","text":"DURI","correct":false},{"id":"283f03b472e12ba313511c7fbd4bcd9c","text":"AURI","correct":true},{"id":"592425dc8e5fd4ddddb711fcb56dcd41","text":"MURI","correct":false},{"id":"19eeb11e145e7494345b431a13df9b60","text":"PURI","correct":true}]},{"id":"n7rouwfc-9cnc-mywz-rj44-v3c021ws4ry3","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following acts like built-in firewalls per instance for your virtual servers?","explanation":"Security Groups act like built-in firewalls for your virtual servers - the rules you create define what is allowed to talk to your instances and how. Although Network Access Control Lists can be used to block or deny traffic, these operate at the subnet level - covering all instances in the subnet with the same ruleset, not per-instance as the question specifies. Route tables tell traffic where it should go next to reach its destination, and an Availability Zone is a collection of datacentres - which isn't relevant in this question. ","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-network-security.html","title":"Amazon EC2 Security Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":true},{"id":"06ea336ee4a57004a721e76f5cdd9083","text":"Network Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"8f36276b8cef5979b167a77e143d894e","text":"Route Tables","correct":false},{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":false}]},{"id":"80c462fa-2fa6-11ea-aec2-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS Support plans provide access to online self-paced labs for training staff?","explanation":"Only the Enterprise support plan provides access to online self-paced labs.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true}]},{"id":"zejpj051-p0tv-b1pt-hvqk-i5pz24d88v68","domain":"tech","question":"Which AWS service allows you to run code without having to worry about provisioning any underlying resources (such as virtual machines, databases etc.)","explanation":"Lambda is the AWS Function-as-a-Service (FaaS) offering that lets you run code without provisioning or managing servers. Elastic Container Service (ECS) uses containers, but still requires management of the underlying servers to some extent. EC2 uses traditional servers, and does require all the other resources to be provisioned and setup. DynamoDB is specifically used for storing information in non-relational databases, and is unable to run code.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/","title":"About Lambda"}],"answers":[{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":true},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"e66f7962b812129e4a3890b1dab122c0","text":"Elastic Container Service","correct":false},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false}]},{"id":"bc537d70-2f37-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following classifications would apply to Kinesis Video Streams?","explanation":"Kinesis Video Streams is an AWS service you can use to store and watch video streams in real time as they are received in the cloud. In addition, you can process and analyze the streams by using third-party solutions that you can get at the AWS Marketplace. So, Kinesis Video Streams is both a media service and an analytics tool.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/","title":"AWS Documentation"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/kinesisvideostreams/latest/dg/what-is-kinesis-video.html","title":"What Is Amazon Kinesis Video Streams?"}],"answers":[{"id":"0b4a1fd2370952e6f7c276106ee02957","text":"Game Development","correct":false},{"id":"ac1697f8b440a0a0dca32da2e95da8bd","text":"Media Services","correct":true},{"id":"091fa9121c047db1dd48c3e2ab5f3c91","text":"Machine Learning","correct":false},{"id":"a768caa988605a2846599cf7e2d0c26a","text":"Analytics","correct":true}]},{"id":"0mdd9dnl-ji3o-hjum-lyr4-wtpoks65v0z9","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements about AWS Region is true?","explanation":"A region is a geographical area divided into Availability Zones. Each region contains at least two publicly accessible Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"bec481a5e2c63bfc93d4922d5845bd2b","text":"Regions are only available in some locations globally","correct":false},{"id":"2cf30d8c571fe080cdd53d0a78db5689","text":"Regions are automatically fully synchronized to contain the same data globally","correct":false},{"id":"1c52cae4b07ea355b6bf0d1522efc7e7","text":"Regions are made up of Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"fddc13d769887bc62fc14c8d844e1aa9","text":"Regions are generally specific geographical areas","correct":true}]},{"id":"57f5e909-774f-43b9-9718-c0b61fc8225c","domain":"security","question":"You are currently running an application in a production environment, but you want to ensure that it is free of vulnerabilities. Which of the following AWS services would you need to use?","explanation":"You will need to turn to Amazon Inspector for security assessment. Not only does it identify vulnerabilities in your application, it will also spot deviations from security best practices. AWS Shield and WAF protect the application from attacks that exploit vulnerabilities, rather than identify them. And Trusted Advisor only provides recommendations on how to improve security.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/inspector/latest/userguide/inspector_introduction.html","title":"What is Amazon Inspector?"}],"answers":[{"id":"41a831f771ef9bece59ed5160e335ae7","text":"AWS Trusted Inspector","correct":false},{"id":"543096643aa6d28d9fac278e9257783d","text":"Amazon Inspector","correct":true},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"769f2c629067645d4b60e13009500c9f","text":"AWS Web Application Firewall (WAF)","correct":false}]},{"id":"rku8juy8-m8eo-xhrd-ap7e-a3nhr9045k2l","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below is TRUE when considering subnets in a VPC?","explanation":"By default, all subnets within a VPC can communicate with each other, without needing any other resources or configuration. NAT Gateway and Internet Gateway work in different scenarios to allow your subnet to communicate with the internet and are not required to communicate between subnets","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonVPC/latest/UserGuide/VPC_Subnets.html","title":"VPCs and Subnets"}],"answers":[{"id":"b5bcf23beb0bab6ed020ef6e8d9026ef","text":"Subnets within a VPC can only communicate with each other if a NAT Gateway is deployed","correct":false},{"id":"bdcce4ddcc3bbe6bca2d1851d91ff3a2","text":"By default, all subnets within a VPC can communicate with each other","correct":true},{"id":"8ff25f40e9a121e4620e1809190ac599","text":"By default, subnets within a VPC cannot communicate with each other","correct":false},{"id":"ecfdf4b74c36d8d497f1023a5b24e38f","text":"Subnets within a VPC can only communicate with each other if an Internet Gateway is deployed","correct":false}]},{"id":"alwhmkiv-aa40-zbsb-1app-zkbeiem7zvs3","domain":"concepts","question":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, for which of the following does AWS not assume responsibility?","explanation":"Customers are responsible for their own customer data in the cloud. AWS manages the Networking, Hypervisor Configuration, and Physical Security","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"AWS shared Responsibility"}],"answers":[{"id":"5dd5aedeaa5de8a95f383a8e014b1e5d","text":"Physical security of AWS facilities","correct":false},{"id":"1b837a3c0786d704da0c00c61b4d57b5","text":"Hypervisors","correct":false},{"id":"6016c2bb7bd8dd79293094d37ebfea3f","text":"Customer data","correct":true},{"id":"a5fa5746370b608090b994a97b49e98b","text":"Networking","correct":false}]},{"id":"prqyybkg-4flz-vdjf-hmny-u1q34ck87hm9","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are AWS compute services?","explanation":"EC2 and Lambda are AWS Compute Services, while RDS is a Database service, and SNS is an Application Integration service.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/products/compute/","title":"AWS Compute"}],"answers":[{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":true},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":true},{"id":"0f41d6f36f8eaee87ea08d9f4b1159e2","text":"RDS","correct":false},{"id":"54afc4697cf03d8e3ec9a05b16380622","text":"SNS","correct":false}]},{"id":"0b2dkrmk-derf-tm5u-h127-w4yffwtldij2","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following are Support Levels offered by AWS?","explanation":"AWS Support has four levels. Basic is their free entitlement for all AWS Customers. The three paid support plans in order of ascending cost are Developer, Business, and Enterprise. Start-up and Individual do not exist as Support Plans","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":true},{"id":"3263b7364a2b2cb3d4697003ef512748","text":"Start-up","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":true},{"id":"2dd4472245a696bc0b4b944db2a8b519","text":"Individual","correct":false}]},{"id":"el8zebxq-qo1d-az5o-l4lp-vmh132hnt1zd","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following Compliance guarantees attests to the fact that the AWS Platform has met the standard required for the secure storage of medical records in the US?","explanation":"A HIPAA certification attests to the fact that the AWS Platform has met the standard required for the secure storage of medical records in the US.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Compliance"},{"url":"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hippa_(disambiguation)","title":"HIPPA or HIPAA"}],"answers":[{"id":"393dceb94f2cac456fd53985a67d72b3","text":"HITECH","correct":false},{"id":"d0a785d52ac4a841f7efdf0098d9ebd5","text":"HIPAA","correct":true},{"id":"dba5359496e7ea71f51ce4da1ee614bd","text":"GLBA","correct":false},{"id":"739f96badcfca6fd03c1e5b17971c9de","text":"HIPPO","correct":false},{"id":"827ec26130c30cc52e3fb178e0ef505c","text":"FERPA","correct":false}]},{"id":"9a62e30f-6366-4ba3-a6f9-29118a4432d8","domain":"billing","question":"When would you use the Reserved Instance pricing model?","explanation":"Reserved instances are a great way of reducing costs on long running applications with predictable workloads. Even if the money is not available to make upfront payments, using Reserved Instances over longer periods can still be useful for cost savings","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"e757909a259f51f248d287636899abda","text":"Ability to bid on the lowest compute price possible","correct":false},{"id":"f5bfd0de9a22ee48b87ae246ed4f4042","text":"CAPEX vs OPEX charging model","correct":true},{"id":"79c233b246a21fbcf2c865dcef7f0791","text":"Predictable workload types","correct":true},{"id":"642a643c75d27712431a1b79c28e8cc5","text":"Unpredictable workloads","correct":false}]},{"id":"4hjaxq6n-z5w0-zfz5-rhia-l14kd19r6656","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are best practices when it comes to securing your AWS account?","explanation":"Creating individual IAM users, using groups to assign them permission and creating a strong password policy are all key components of securing your AWS account. The root user should only be used in emergencies, therefore there should be no need to have Root Access Keys which allow the root user Programmatic access - any Programmatic access should use something other than the root account. It is not possible to delete the root password, and this should be securely, safely stored and not used in any applications!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_root-user.html","title":"The AWS Account Root User"}],"answers":[{"id":"5d44464e3d76ef6a6641b8044d7d2525","text":"Activate MFA on the Root Account.","correct":true},{"id":"07623cbc5a5f07bde8c94a98256a165f","text":"Use groups to assign permissions.","correct":true},{"id":"9c2eddf5402bf5f69b4cfd6f6cbb82ef","text":"Store your Root account keys on your application for easy access.","correct":false},{"id":"b109f832528a7df4db93f8f1016812b4","text":"Create individual IAM users.","correct":true},{"id":"af5257e2e32921faab688050c9de091e","text":"Apply an IAM password policy.","correct":true},{"id":"427d69ad60aa7d9c68a9214e103fc80a","text":"Delete your Root account password.","correct":false},{"id":"561f3fa869736d8c37dd07fc1284f00f","text":"Delete your Root access keys.","correct":true}]},{"id":"vsrs40em-06ny-u7sl-hdn2-xstt497klvo3","domain":"concepts","question":"Generally speaking, what is the minimum number of Availability Zones per AWS Region?","explanation":"At least 2 Availability Zones will be publicly available per AWS Region, with most regions having 3 Availability Zones available. There are specific exceptions to this rule, such as the Osaka Local Region, which has only one AZ by design.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"c81e728d9d4c2f636f067f89cc14862c","text":"2","correct":true},{"id":"c4ca4238a0b923820dcc509a6f75849b","text":"1","correct":false},{"id":"eccbc87e4b5ce2fe28308fd9f2a7baf3","text":"3","correct":false},{"id":"a87ff679a2f3e71d9181a67b7542122c","text":"4","correct":false}]},{"id":"qlfvvg3n-igqt-be79-1bph-rx4nrjmqmm25","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below statements are correct in relation to security responsibilities in AWS?","explanation":"AWS is responsible for the security OF the cloud - the security of components that run the cloud service. The customer is responsible for security IN the cloud -- that is, the security of their AWS resources and data.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"7c5f3942078ece3769cd1bcbde2bdabb","text":"As an AWS customer, you are responsible for the security IN the cloud","correct":true},{"id":"d1f8c47a806feef1c562619b465cb202","text":"AWS is responsible for the security OF the cloud","correct":true},{"id":"0369ed76a5e4ccb3887e44fe8a7c8703","text":"AWS is responsible for the security IN the cloud","correct":false},{"id":"a1b79685a2bbdb6743277416ad663c24","text":"As an AWS customer, you are responsible for the security OF the cloud","correct":false}]},{"id":"ae4qnqr4-q2bm-f2dr-mvle-moqon5u5blu8","domain":"tech","question":"How can Auto Scaling help your resources handle changes in demand?","explanation":"Auto Scaling allows you to automatically add or remove EC2 instances based on conditions you specify - these can include such things as at a specific time, or depending on how busy your application. Autoscaling cannot change the size of existing instances, nor can it add or change storage on an instance.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/","title":"About Auto Scaling"}],"answers":[{"id":"8d190956e7e4664d306007a2601517cd","text":"By increasing or decreasing the size of your storage based on conditions you specify","correct":false},{"id":"168c8ea8bcef87e54350e112c4067deb","text":"By adding or removing storage based on conditions you specify","correct":false},{"id":"12545090042f77a088ab7bcaa6de4d72","text":"By increasing or decreasing the size of your EC2 instances based on conditions you specify","correct":false},{"id":"71b888b01492a657424f4f82588f0d28","text":"By adding or removing EC2 instances from your EC2 fleet based on conditions you specify","correct":true}]},{"id":"d05a0228-8d82-4cef-8dfb-4e2cb3856a9f","domain":"security","question":"According to the Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is AWS responsible for?","explanation":"Protecting the infrastructure that runs all of the services in the AWS Cloud is the responsibility of AWS. Such services include EC2 infrastructure - the hardware compute platform for running EC2 instances and Amazon Virtual Private Cloud, or VPC, which enables customers to provision a logically isolated section of the AWS Cloud to launch their resources. The subnets, security groups, and network access control lists configured in the VPC are the responsibility of the customer.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/vpc/","title":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"28aaf85b7ba1e63aa22c1c645a4c22e4","text":"Elastic Cloud Compute (EC2) infrastructure","correct":true},{"id":"c33dcb724e4d74e54dbc8347d4402690","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud","correct":true},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"06ea336ee4a57004a721e76f5cdd9083","text":"Network Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":false}]},{"id":"rc4dwp79-ix5s-h912-sdcj-9gmmhl6zacte","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following is AWS' managed DDoS protection service?","explanation":"AWS Shield is AWS' managed DDoS protection service at Layer 4. AWS WAF provides protection from common exploits against your web applications at Layer 7, and does not protect against DDoS attacks.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/shield/?nc2=h_l3_dm","title":"About AWS Shield"}],"answers":[{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"303a25c2935ec1fdb01208b6f4f65688","text":"Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":true}]},{"id":"9n50o6rz-03s4-bpbd-i7dy-36qby4h0ka5x","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for when running an RDS database on AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model for managed services, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance), as well as making sure the underlying OS and application is up to date. You as the user are responsible for keeping your data secure.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"2b6b76aaf679124f3da7b20c5df23923","text":"Updating the database software","correct":false},{"id":"8782b4a6bdea28cea082df1413a7f818","text":"Controlling access to the compute hardware","correct":false},{"id":"0266c79a8678f6881cc2857043b46509","text":"Controlling access to the network hardware","correct":false},{"id":"86da12905838c932b65844a3fa01aa08","text":"Updating the operating system","correct":false},{"id":"57b862a3c428d3330f8c03216acd2c16","text":"Controlling access to the database","correct":true}]},{"id":"f9bc3071-e017-426b-bb59-bebf2bb60194","domain":"billing","question":"You need an AWS support plan for your production workloads, but want to keep costs to a minimum. Which of the following plans should you choose?","explanation":"The Business Support plan is specifically designed for production workloads in AWS. On one end, Basic Support is included for all AWS customers, and Developer Support plan is best suited for experimenting or testing in AWS. On the other end, there’s the Enterprise Support plan, which is ideal for business and mission-critical workloads.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false}]},{"id":"1bq7soel-r0fa-9nu9-nkn7-tsl4tdqsb4ne","domain":"security","question":"You would like to give an application running on one of your EC2 instances access to an S3 bucket - what is the best way to implement this?","explanation":"The recommended method to assign permissions to apps running in EC2 is to use IAM roles. Making the bucket public could work, but will also expose all the data to the internet and is not secure. The other methods are also less secure than using IAM roles and are not recommended in this case.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/best-practices.html","title":"IAM Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"506f9dca07627c4a0037801fd015ae25","text":"Use an IAM user for the application","correct":false},{"id":"6d5604611f5103e032eae843cc2d3861","text":"Give the application a set of Access Keys","correct":false},{"id":"200bfcc1caf00feb47c6ca792e965a17","text":"Make the bucket public","correct":false},{"id":"1e3f1e527016bc7fae2856f9acfd533a","text":"Assign the instance an IAM role","correct":true}]},{"id":"1wf5g4cl-1eei-cxmu-red3-wkm59ywgq86h","domain":"tech","question":"With AWS Relational Database Service (RDS), which of the following are you responsible for?","explanation":"You are responsible only for the optimization of your application that uses RDS - AWS will take care of the rest as this is considered a Managed Service.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/","title":"About RDS"}],"answers":[{"id":"7b4eef372e52b848a7e0f93e59b06d70","text":"All of these","correct":false},{"id":"89f8bb80ca1403422295c6ad48f8cac7","text":"Database backups","correct":false},{"id":"bc967dc2d57e6eff184a821bf7577a80","text":"Scaling","correct":false},{"id":"a514531b35c90598677ddee7c4b1afd9","text":"The optimization of your application using RDS","correct":true},{"id":"6bb1aca01fa54044f3ec9ae581b4620f","text":"Operating system installation and patching","correct":false},{"id":"5f4dc8e976d91d69670d0a272e0ee6e3","text":"Database software installation and patching","correct":false}]},{"id":"ism9fl1z-nho7-nn22-5sn8-4qqdyyu4pyeq","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is AWS’ event-driven, serverless compute service?","explanation":"Lambda is AWS’ event-driven, serverless compute service that allows you to run code without having to deploy or manage any of the underlying resources such as EC2 instances.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/","title":"About Lambda"}],"answers":[{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":true},{"id":"b21eea42e76007ac061cf37a5a41037d","text":"Lightsail","correct":false},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"3d6cbd7db2a4fa389808ea6f4a5fc1bc","text":"Elastic Beanstalk","correct":false}]},{"id":"7gpfi6zh-od3t-hgmy-7puh-d955spmckv2u","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound cloud design?","explanation":"Build your systems to be scalable, use disposable resources, reduce infrastructure to code, and, please, assume EVERYTHING will fail sooner or later. Servers should be treated like cattle, where the exist to serve a function, and for a generally limited period of time, as opposed to pets which are kept and cared for over very long periods of time. There is no reason to limit the number of 3rd party services, if it makes the most sense in the case of the design at hand. Tightly-coupled components result in hard dependencies between different services, and usually lead to issues with either an applications health, or its scalability.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"c4feabf8a0fd67917d77220d3b036291","text":"Tightly-coupled components","correct":false},{"id":"af41549605744cf23f27cbc14458bf82","text":"Infrastructure as code","correct":true},{"id":"fd3ca13906a4c1e05f791d27dbc66914","text":"Disposable resources","correct":true},{"id":"9cb4d987bd4d50912c60823480c86972","text":"Treat your servers like pets, not cattle.","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"31ae780d15d60c68f6689a039e6f3802","text":"Assume *everything* will fail.","correct":true},{"id":"df89f307a97b6ecf5647735dcd89f7c8","text":"Limit the number of 3rd-party services.","correct":false}]},{"id":"i9b6xlrs-qiap-mdwa-l2pv-m72run0d25np","domain":"security","question":"When considering the security of an AWS EC2 instance, which of the below are Users responsible for?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, users are entirely responsible for the security, patching and maintenance of AWS IaaS services such as EC2. AWS will only take care of the underlying hardware used to provide the service. ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"51f337ee03b5fc05c3edf7764c0633b1","text":"Physical and Environmental controls","correct":false},{"id":"8dee4c58b0c64b645b2052b129768b98","text":"Security Configuration","correct":true},{"id":"b6b41cd6bd59164805860b107633ce14","text":"Patching and maintenance of OS & Applications","correct":true},{"id":"6485477a46494966f254ee5c23dd8ba7","text":"Patching and maintenance of server hardware","correct":false}]},{"id":"smnrxkfv-dk56-snvh-i93e-or0vfomvccbz","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are characteristics of cloud computing?","explanation":"The on-demand delivery via the internet of services with pay-as-you-go pricing characterizes cloud computing. Services incurred from a cloud services provider are operating expenses, not capital expenses. Capital Expenditure (CAPEX) is less common with the cloud, in favour of Operational Expenditure (OPEX). Skills and training for personnel are required to leverage Cloud Computing","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"9b670633c5238ca5a17dd651c3a63662","text":"No extra skills or training are required.","correct":false},{"id":"481f1c72f1007c1ac8e4a484b47af4f2","text":"Cloud charges are Capital Expenditures.","correct":false},{"id":"ebc744edbd870e96fe9e680b407ad053","text":"On-demand delivery","correct":true},{"id":"2b34d3fef0b313e0047a2557d9842378","text":"Pay-as-you-go pricing","correct":true},{"id":"dcfe379beaf88dbe9d59e7fcecf6f98a","text":"Services are delivered via the Internet.","correct":true}]},{"id":"1cfba8e0-0fb8-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"billing","question":"You have EC2 and RDS instances, Redshift and Elasticsearch clusters, and an SNS topic in your AWS environment. Which of these services support reserved pricing?","explanation":"Amazon SNS is the only one of the five mentioned services that does not have reserved pricing. On the other hand, Amazon EC2, RDS, Redshift, and Elasticsearch do.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/pricing/","title":"Amazon RDS Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/redshift/pricing/","title":"Amazon Redshift Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticsearch-service/pricing/","title":"Amazon Elasticsearch Service Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"0221d4f5950f35dfcf98f6a60f60d20d","text":" Elasticsearch and SNS","correct":false},{"id":"3ec389f2e16e0e0443f3ef49d2b58d05","text":"EC2 and RDS","correct":false},{"id":"65e4dd05e0a1392e55661f27717e96cb","text":"RDS, Redshift, Elasticsearch, and SNS","correct":false},{"id":"fcb02ff285a97f0ed386c6cfe36b02f4","text":"EC2, RDS, Redshift, and Elasticsearch","correct":true},{"id":"9d6fbf729ccc02278cc50176a91ed3fe","text":"EC2, Redshift, and SNS","correct":false}]},{"id":"ff57921e-2faa-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following statements are true of the AWS Free Tier?","explanation":"All statements listed here are correct except for one. If you don’t use all your Free Tier benefits within the month, they don’t roll over to the next month.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/billing-free-tier.html","title":"Using the AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"aec630c6387bfee54b18d0ca80ea994c","text":"Unused benefits that the Free Tier provides in a given month roll over to the next month.","correct":false},{"id":"fca0d4d0e7ba8ff0a86efa806423c98d","text":"AWS starts charging the regular rates for usage of services and resources when the Free Tier expires.","correct":true},{"id":"e0a5844f80154f67479f312499e75d1a","text":"Usage must be kept below the Free Tier limits to avoid charges.","correct":true},{"id":"8723f65debe98902ae71daeac7ca33e0","text":"Upon creation of an AWS account, the user is automatically signed up for the Free Tier for 12 months.","correct":true}]},{"id":"2d6841a4-2163-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"In AWS, you can stop or terminate instances when not in use. Which of the following concepts describes this capability?","explanation":"Elasticity denotes the ability to increase or reduce the number or capabilities of AWS resources when needed. In this case, stopping or terminating instances means that you are reducing the number of AWS resources used in your environment.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":true},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"857defc5b4c6f1fef867a03c300bdd29","text":"Loose Coupling","correct":false},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false}]}]}}}}
